Hex Pulse Chain. Everything is looking
good. So, last time we spoke, we were
looking at this candle right here. And
interesting enough, this is actually an
engulfing candle. So, this was actually
pretty bearish. But the the following
day is what really determines if it
follows through or not, obviously.
Right. So, we had a nice move up,
re-engul.
So everything is going pretty much as I
kind of expected to. I actually think
like this is the most bullish I've been
on Hex and Postchain
since the beginning really. It's looking
really good. I don't I think sellers
have finally been exhausted and I think
there's only buyers left. Like it's
really as simple as that. Everyone who
was going to sell has probably sold by
now. And then you have people stepping
in and selling. And when they step in
and sell, that's it. There's like one
guy who might is come from out of
nowhere. He might dump and knock the
price down, but that's it. And it's just
the buyers and it gets bought right back
up. You can see it on the chart. Dumps
and then that's it. And then just tick
tick tick tick tick tick tick tick tick
tick tick tick tick. And then somebody
dumps again. Tick, tick, tick, tick,
tick, tick. Done. It's It's over and
over again. So, until that stops, until
we get follow through on the sales,
I'm pretty bullish, man. I know it
sounds weird. These videos aren't
getting the most engagement cuz I'm sure
people have been bullish on PEX and
Postchain for the past near 10 years,
but I wasn't, but I am now. So, we're
getting a breakthrough. We got a new
swing highs here. Um, Nest Hex on ETH.
Now, it's just a matter of when does do
the when does it stop? I don't know.
Let's look at some other things on
Postgame. So, PI a lot of people asked
me to talk about PI. There's a lot of
people that are really bullish on PI.
So, what I had the epiphany um last
night and I said, you know what, let's
just onboard everybody to more. So I
said, who would be the what would be the
first the best community? What's the
best token community to on board first?
And I said, it's PI. They're the most
rabbit next to the Hexacans. So PI is
coming to more. I don't want to say too
much, but it's it's coming pretty soon.
I know you guys are probably wondering
how how are you going to what are you
going to do? It's so obvious. It's one
of those things like so obvious. So be
on the lookout for that. Piains p what
do we call you guys? Pyers.
Um
yeah. So that's coming to more. That's
going to be great. And it's going to be
a lot a lot more coming to more. But we
got Pulse is looking good too. Pulse had
a a big drop. And look at that. It's
just
this is bullish. These are bullish
things, man. These are bullish
activities.
You see a red candle and then it's just
like eating it up. And this the opposite
of what's been going on, which is green
candles getting eaten. Now we're eating
the red candles. So, you can see when we
got to this level, huge sales come in
and then it's just like there's no more
there's no more selling. the sellers are
getting exhausted fast. So, I'm not
saying this is going to go on forever,
but it's going on right now. You know,
that's what's important is what's
happening right now. And that's what's
happening. We're getting drops and then
they're trying up Hex on Pulse Chain.
It's following a similar path to Pulse
Chain. So, it's looking good. Nice
bounces
clearing resistances.
More. Same thing here. More is looking
more like the hex chart. It's not really
dipping as hard, but it's looking good.
Let's check out Pulseex is another one
that might come to the more platform.
It's looking pretty good. It's looking
pulse pulseesque.
These are very good moves, man. like
this is what you want to see if you want
to if you want to be bullish.
This is what you want to see. So, we
know the same thing is going across the
board. Everything is be recovering. INC
is looking good, but Inc. looks a little
bit heavier. It's lagging behind for
sure. So, we have Hex on Pulse Chain
currently up from the bottom. We'll go
from the bottom on this [snorts]
266%.
Then you got PostChain
from the bottom it's up just 58%.
Hex on Ethereum let's see how much that
is up from the bottom 21%.
So, it looks like Hex on PulseChain, if
we're going from the bottom, right, Hex
on PulseChain is up the most,
followed by Hex on Ethereum.
And then PulseChain, Pulse X from the
bottom is up 90%. So, it's Pulse X is up
more than Pulse. And then you have Inc.
that is up 80%. So, it's up more than it
looks. So, everything is looking good.
Now, of course, people are say, you
know, from the, you know, you're down a
lot. Yeah, sure. But if you started
buying like I did a couple days ago,
[laughter]
a couple weeks ago maybe
or if you waited until recently, you
know, every just because you know you're
down this much from the from the top. It
didn't take much buying in these. I not
inc chart. I'll say what what I did is I
bought Hex. You know, just because Hex
is down a lot doesn't mean I'm not up
from buying all of this. You know, I
started DCNA not that long ago. It got
to the point where it's like, man, this
stuff is like dust now. I can get a
bunch of the hex and stake it. And now
that's paying off. Like, I might have I
might have doubled my entire holdings,
you know, cuz it's so cheap. I didn't
have to put much economic energy to get
a bigger position. If I didn't double
it, I at least added a third, you know,
to my entire position. And now it's
looking, you know, not as bad. It's
actually looking pretty good. I mean, I
haven't checked my portfolio, but I
mean, that's a big gain. So, it's all
about where you're playing from. If you
if you're somebody, you know, and that's
why you're not seeing a lot of
excitement yet because a lot of people
are didn't do that. Most people are just
holding on to what they have and they're
just riding with that and they're like,
"Oh, we're just back to prices." But, I
mean, we're back to the lows from back
here. That was a minute ago back in
April.
Um, so April 25. So, it's all about
perspective. You know, you got someone
like me. I'm not trying I'm not trying
to rub it in. I'm just trying to
rationalize these videos for you because
you're like, "Man, you're still down." I
zoom out and I look at I look at all
that red. It's like, yeah, but what if
you just started buying a couple weeks
ago, you know, a couple months ago, back
from March even, you're up double. You
didn't even have to buy the bottom. So,
the people that did that, they're kind
of loud right now, but um it's still
pretty early. I don't think we start
getting excit hearing a lot of chatter
until we make another strong move up to
these levels here. Um, but yeah, man,
it's kind of it's kind of uh it's tough
because I get it like yeah, it's down a
lot, you know, it went down a lot, but
if you zoom in, a lot of people say zoom
out, maybe zoom in.
Um, it's looking good. So, we're going
to see how these candles play out the
rest of the day. They're holding it up.
Um, we'll see if some sellers step in.
Um, also go stake some more. APR is on
Pulse Chain. APR is
65 past APR APY. I'm just building the
ladder out. So, it looks like in about
um two months, we're going to start
getting some stakes that end. And I'm
curious to see what these will be at.
So, I'm just staking every day. You
know, I built this for myself really cuz
I like staking and I wanted to stake
something that doesn't have inflation.
So, be on the lookout for uh PI.
It shouldn't be long. Fuel that's coming
too. But I don't think I Oh, what
happened to fuel? No, fuel is pretty
much done. I'm just waiting for the
market to But I think it's about I think
it's about time. Like maybe we'll do
fuel first. But I think fuel needs more
momentum. Fuel is a protocol that's
going to need momentum. So, we're going
to need to talk about it. PI sorry got a
community doesn't there's no real rush
for what's coming on that you can get in
whenever. Um [clears throat] feel too,
but you know what I mean. Um, that's
about it, man. I'll talk to you on the
next one.